foreign
hi it's Ken and I hope you've just
enjoyed those pictures that you saw I
thought some of those were a little bit
embarrassing for me and of course I'm
proud of some of the others I'm your new
CAO Chief agency officer for Prudential
Vietnam and I'm really excited to be
here talking to you today by the video
you may want to know a few things about
me I'm an American I'm 50 years old and
I have two lovely daughters one is 18
and the other is 23. I'm happy to say
that both are living now in the U.S my
18 year old is entering University this
fall and my 23 year old has just been
licensed in California as an insurance
agent and she happens to be representing
Jackson National Insurance products
which makes her essentially a Prudential
agent just like yourself I've been
living in Hong Kong and working in Hong
Kong for the last 12 years I spent the
first 10 years of my 22 years in
California working as an agent a broker
I've been a ga a leader a trainer
so I've had quite a bit of experience
and I've had many different jobs in many
different countries
I spent 12 years as I said in Asia
working for companies like AIA Sun Life
Financial and of course Prudential when
I started in the business I had a tough
time I became in as an agent I was
nearly fired asked to leave the company
somehow I stuck around and I started
making some sales
I became a leader when I was a leader
like all leaders I struggled struggled
to recruit struggled to train struggled
to motivate the team I've done a lot of
the business and even recently I've left
the business and I've come back
because I think what happens is this
business you're in the business but the
business comes inside you
clear things like paying claims I paid
claims for young babies I've paid claims
to fathers and and every one of those
times that's had a great impact on me
wondering after 22 years in 12 different
countries why I'm so excited about being
Prudential Vietnam's Chief agency
officer well let me tell you there's
quite a few reasons and some of them
start with why Vietnam is so exciting
did you know the average age is just 26
years old that makes me a grandfather in
most countries but I'm not one yet the
GDP last year in 2011 2011 grew 6.3
percent
when you compare that to what's
happening in the United States on one
side Europe on the other it really
stands out as a country that's going
places the political environment is
stable the country is safe
the people the food the culture I love
it all these are some of the most
talented individuals in Asia right here
in Prudential Vietnam believe me I've
been to so many markets I've seen so
many agencies and so many agency staff
this really is a concentration of
excellent agency Talent you keep showing
that month on month and year on year
making records then beating records last
month we recruited
9805 agents fantastic so how are we
going to keep going how do we keep
making records how do we keep beating
records we've got a new structure an AED
that you're just hearing about this
thing has been well thought out we're
designing this so we can support you
train you and help you deliver the kind
of results that you deserve as agents
and leaders
going forward we're going to continue to
pour our efforts towards developing
leaders so the leaders can help train
and motivate and promote their own
agents we're going to work with proof
Champions that way we're going to work
with Pro Elite so the agents that choose
the career as an agent can really
prosper and grow and be full-time in
this business we're also looking at some
exciting initiatives one of them that I
like to call multi-channel agency you're
going to hear more about that so stay
tuned you've heard about Mission
possible there's a lot of things about
Mission possible that excite me and the
most important is defining what we think
is impossible
and then a finding a way to make it
happen
with your help your belief and your
passion Mission possible is going to be
one of the most exciting things to
happen in Prudential Vietnam in the last
several years
let's talk a little bit more about
Mission possible you know I know and I
recognize and understand that we are in
a very tough economic environment we've
got high interest rates we've got
challenges with competition
we also have an economic environment
globally that is making life difficult
for everybody
but you know Mission possible is all
about recognizing those putting in
places and ideas to address them and
moving on and accomplishing what we know
is possible look Prudential Vietnam goes
from record making to record-breaking
month by month quarter by quarter in
year by year and I really do believe in
you I believe in our agents I believe in
our leaders and I most importantly I
believe in the staff and the country and
the potential of the Vietnam
you know just three years ago the
building behind me proof Plaza here in
Ho Chi Minh City was told that it was
unsafe
and we looked inside and we found it
wasn't unsafe there were cracks yes
just like we look around and see some
cracks on the economy and cracks on the
other at macro and microeconomics but
that doesn't matter we went inside
Prudential Plaza and we scraped it down
we plastered it up we painted it we put
in new offices it now houses some of the
core functions of Prudential Vietnam
most importantly to me is agency
training agency development and some of
the agency offices as well as a
fantastic customer service center just
like the other 230 around the country
where people come to go and interact
with Prudential Vietnam staff
another fantastic thing that no one
thought possible more than three six
months ago was this beautiful river that
I'm standing on from end to end it runs
through Ho Chi Minh City and not long
ago it was dirty it was polluted it was
unsafe
but now today we can see a beautiful
River smells clean and it looks
fantastic the government is embarked
upon a very very long project it goes
from the bay all the way to Highway One
and along this route you're now seeing
families go for night walks you're
seeing people come to sit and chat and
have coffee
things that we were thought were
impossible
actually became possible and I know over
the next six months we're going to work
together agency staff the whole company
is going to get behind you so you can do
what we know you're capable of and
helping us close this year out in a
fantastic way so you can benefit as well
and I look forward to meeting you and
working with you all around the country
and I'm going to spend the next six
months touching as many of you and
shaking hands as I can I wish I was
there today to say hi and to cheer you
on but I'm choosing this message to tell
you how I feel about you and I hope
you've enjoyed it hope you've gotten to
know me a little bit better and I look
forward to getting to know you better
thank you very much come on